我们必须快点。
We must hurry.
地球不会再存活多久了。
The planet won't survive much longer.
你确定吗?
Are you sure about this?
恐怕这是唯一的办法了。
I'm afraid it's the only way.
氪星就要死了。
Krypton is about to die.
但你，亲爱的儿子，会活下去的。
But you, dear son, will live on.
Krypto,不!
Krypto, no!
哦!Krypto !
Oh! Krypto!
不。
No.
我们的孩子需要一个朋友。
Our boy will need a friend.
照看好我们的儿子。
Watch over our son.
好了，醒醒，伙计。这是walk-o整。
All right, wake up, buddy. It is walk-o'clock.
也许我应该让他睡一觉?
Maybe I should let him sleep?
好吧，我让他睡了。
Okay, I let him sleep.
好吧。
All right.
这对我们俩来说都不愉快。
This is unpleasant for both of us.
不。不,不。不,不。
No. No, no. No, no.
嗯。
Hmm.
五个……五分钟。
Five more... Five more minutes.
我起来。
And I'm up.
好的,Krypto。
Okay, Krypto.
我们去散步。
We'll go for a walk.
哇!
Whoa!
♪你让我活了起来♪
♪ Ooh you make me live ♪
♪这个世界能给我什么就给什么
♪ Whatever this world can give to me ♪
♪我看到的只有你♪
♪ It's you you're all I see ♪
♪你让我活了起来♪
♪ Ooh you make me live ♪
♬你是我最好的朋友
♪ You're the best friend ♪
♪我曾经有过的♪
♪ That I ever had ♪
♪。♪我和你在一起这么久了
- ♪ I've been with you such a long time ♪
♪你是我的阳光我想让你知道
♪ You're my sunshine and I want you to know ♪
嗯?
Huh?
♪……♪我真的爱你
♪ ...I really love you ♪
♪你是我最好的朋友
♪ Oh you're the best friend ♪
♪你让我活了起来♪
♪ Ooh you make me live ♪
♪每当这个世界对我残酷♪
♪ Whenever this world is cruel to me ♪
♪我有你帮我原谅♪
♪ I got you to help me forgive ♪
♪你让我活了起来♪
♪ Ooh you make me live ♪
♪……我曾经拥有过的
♪ ...that I ever had ♪
♪你知道我永远不会孤单
♪ You know I'll never be lonely ♪
♪你是我的唯一♪
♪ You're my only one ♪
♬我喜欢♬的东西
♪ And I love the things ♪
♪我真的很喜欢你做的事情♪
♪ I really love the things that you do ♪
♬你是我最好的朋友
♪ Oh you're my best friend ♪
Mxyzptlk先生终于被打败了。
Mister Mxyzptlk has finally been defeated.
原来，他只需要倒着念他的名字。
Turns out, he just needed to say his name backwards.
我是露易丝·莱恩，来自大都会。
From Metropolis, I'm Lois Lane.
嘿,露易丝。
Hey, Lois.
我知道你喜欢这个，所以我从巴黎给你买了一个。
I know you like these, so I got you one from actual Paris.
我不知道我为什么那样说。
I don't know why I said it like that.
我从43街给你买了一个。
And I got you one of these from 43rd Street.
离我的路足足有三个街区远。
Which is, like, a full three blocks out of my way.
在高峰时间吗?
During rush hour?
这就像我要飞到火星一样。
Wow, that's like me flying to Mars.
什么?你能飞吗?
What? You can fly?
我一直以为斗篷只是个可爱的装饰品。
I always thought the cape was just a cute accessory.
哦!所以你觉得我很可爱。
Oh! So you think I'm cute.
我说斗篷很可爱。
I said the cape was cute.
你觉得我很可爱。
You think I'm cute.
我们现在在舔脸吗?
Are we lickin' faces right now?
因为如果我们要舔脸，我就得加入…
Because if we're lickin' faces, I gotta get in on...
哦，这是什么?
Oh, what do I have here?
捏的布鲁斯!
Squeezy Bruce!
获取!
Fetch!
小狗，快起来!
Pup, up and away!
好了，我们说到哪了?
Okay, where were we?
捏的布鲁斯检索。
Squeezy Bruce retrieved.
嘿，那些家伙看起来很有趣。
Hey, those guys look fun.
你去和他们玩怎么样?
How about you go play with them?
所以我在吃自己的呕吐物，然后…所以，我在吃我自己的…所以我……我…我知道你躲进了你的蝙蝠洞，但没人能躲过正义的长鼻子。
So I'm eating my own vomit, and then the... So, I'm eating my own... So I'm... I'm... I see you've retreated to your Batcave, but nobody can hide from the long snoot of justice.
嗯。
Hmm.
然后我说"如果你不想让我在地毯上蹭屁股，那就去铺硬木地板"
And then I says, "If you don't want me rubbing my butt in the carpet, get hardwood floors."
Squeezy Bruce被找回来了。
Squeezy Bruce has been retrieved.
等等，你知道这是谁吗?
Wait, do you know who this is?
是超级狗氪星。
It's Krypto the Super dog.
好的。你可以拿走我的爪印。
Okay. You can have my pawtograph.
听着，恐怕我只能签一个，否则我要签一整天了。
Listen, I'm afraid I gotta keep it to just one, or I'll be signing all day.
失陪了，我得把这个还给我儿子。
Now, if you'll excuse me, I gotta get this back to my boy.
-他不想要。-不好意思，什么?
- He doesn't want it. - I'm sorry, what?
Outside-Underpants先生。
Mr. Outside-Underpants.
他不想要玩具。
He doesn't want the toy.
他想摆脱你。
He's trying to get rid of ya.
什么?那太荒唐了。
What? That's ridiculous.
超人和我形影不离。
Superman and I are inseparable.
我是他的坐骑或死。
I'm his ride or die.
噢,是吗?
Oh, yeah?
这些天你睡在哪里?
Where you, uh, sleeping these days?
我和超人一起睡在床上。
I sleep in bed with Supes.
除非露易丝在这里过夜，那我就得搬到我在地板上的特别位置。
Except when Lois stays over, then I have to move to my extra special spot on the floor.
残酷的。
Brutal.
同样的事情也发生在我身上。
Same thing happened to me.
南希有了未婚妻，一切都结束了。
Nancy got a fiancee and it was all over.
那是法语“拜拜，狗”的意思。
That's French for "Bye-bye, dog."
是啊，你可没我那么有超能力。
Yeah, well, you don't get Supes like I get Supes.
我是说，他当然会约会，但他永远不会爱任何人，除了…我爱你。
I mean, sure, the guy dates, but he will never love anyone except for... I love you.
你还好吗?
Um, are you okay?
我?是的,我……我很好。
Me? Yes, I'm... I'm fine.
我没事，我完全... 没事?
I am fine. I'm totally... Fine?
好吧，聊得不错。英镑。
All right, good talk. Pound it out.
这听起来可能有点疯狂，但既然我们在一起了，我觉得克里普托被忽略了?
This might sound crazy, but now that we're together, I think Krypto feels left out?
是的。我想我算是他唯一的朋友了。
Yeah. I guess I'm, kind of, his only friend.
这是甜的。
That's sweet.
但如果他也有个新朋友，他可能会更开心。
But maybe he'd be happier if he had a new friend, too.
早上好,朋友。
Good morning, friends.
所以它开始。
So it begins.
卡尔会像时钟一样，试图和帕蒂调情。
Like clockwork, Carl will try to flirt with Patty.
噢!那是新的香水吗?
Ooh! Is that new perfume?
这是猫尿。
It's cat pee.
零博弈。
And have zero game.
给这只帅气的狗狗足够的时间…你在干什么，艾斯?
Giving this handsome canine just enough time to... What you doin', Ace?
我要疯了，PB。
I'm bustin' loose, PB.
受够了这个笼子。
Sick of this whole cage situation.
哦,我的女神。
Oh, my goddess.
这就像神奇女侠用她的屈服手镯逃离了毒博士的秘密藏身处一样。
This is just like when Wonder Woman used her Bracelets of Submission to escape Doctor Poison's secret hideout.
喜欢……这个!
Like... this!
好的。不完全是这样。
Okay. Not exactly like this.
要是被救援小姐抓住了怎么办?
What if the rescue lady catches you?
然后把你锁在里屋?
And locks you in the back room?
他们只听舒缓的爵士乐。
Where they only listen to smooth jazz.
放松,芯片。我让我的姑娘默顿放哨。
Relax, Chip. I got my girl, Merton, running lookout.
这些偷窥者什么都不会错过。
These peepers don't miss a thing.
如果救援女士来了，你会知道的。
If the rescue lady's coming, you'll know it.
完美的。因为我差点就…不。
Perfect. Because I almost got myself out of the... Nope.
我想救星来了!
I think the rescue lady's coming!
谢谢你,默顿。
Thanks, Merton.
这是一个…那是个好机会。
That's a... that's a good catch.
我支持你，艾斯。
I'm rooting for you, Ace.
但你难道不想被收养感受一个独居中年人的温暖拥抱吗?
But don't you wanna get adopted and feel the warm embrace of a middle-aged person who lives alone?
是的。他会成为你最好的新朋友。
Yeah. Who will be your new best friend.
你们是我最好的朋友，傻瓜。
You're my best friends, dummies.
你们都跟我去农场。
And you're all coming with me to the farm.
我喜欢听他讲农场!
I love when he talks about the farm!
农场北部。
The farm upstate.
一个未被驯服的天堂，在那里动物们自由奔跑，他们彼此关爱，互相保护。
An untamed paradise where animals run free and they love and protect one another.
生菜长在树上。
And the lettuce grows on trees.
没有避难所阿姨监视我们的一举一动。不。
No shelter lady watching our every move. Nope.
这是一个100%的动物农场。
It's a 100% animal farm.
这听起来一点都不不祥。
That doesn't sound ominous at all.
它是完美的。
It's perfect.
等我把我们都弄出去，我们就去那里。
And when I get us all outta here, well, that's where we're gonna go.
狗是对的。
The dog is right.
他应该寻求自己的自由。
He should seek his freedom.
你看到了吗?露露得到它。
You see that? Lulu gets it.
他必须消灭所有阻挡他的人!
And he must destroy all who stand in his way!
哇。好吧，那只是个转折。
Wow. Well, that just took a turn.
你可以拿你的傻农场开玩笑，但我有那个装置!
You may kid yourself with your silly farm, but I have the device!
因为，不久的将来，当星宿连成一线时，这个装置将带给我终极力量，我将不仅是自由!
For, one day soon, when the stars align, the device will bring me ultimate power and I will be more than free!
“将不仅仅是自由!”
"Will be more than free!"
完全正确。
Exactly.
露露，不管他们在你身上做了什么实验，都给你少了几基尼的猪。
Lulu, whatever they tested on you in that lab, left you a few guineas short of a pig.
那个装置就是一堆垃圾。
That device is just a pile of garbage.
你害怕我的才华。
You fear my brilliance.
退到阴影。
Recede into shadows.
保持眼神交流。
Maintain eye contact.
退到阴影。
Recede into shadows.
好了，孩子，我马上回来给你个惊喜。
All right, boy, I'll be right back with a surprise.
我会留在这里，用我的秘密身份摆姿势。
And I will remain here, posing under my secret identity.
肯特树皮。
Bark Kent.
你最近怎么样，普通的狗狗?
So, what is new with you, fellow normal dog?
前几天我咬了那个联邦快递的人。
Uh, I bit the FedEx guy the other day.
啊,不错。
Ah, fine job.
他为谁工作?
Who was he working for?
佐德?末日军团?
General Zod? The Legion of Doom?
联邦快递。
FedEx.
当然!前任联盟。
Of course! The federation of exes.
不值得信任。
Not to be trusted.
我的主人怎么这么久才来?
What is taking my owner so long?
肯特先生，你想再找一只宠物吗?
So, Mr. Kent, you're looking for another pet, huh?
嗯，我的狗是最好的。
Well, my dog's the best.
但我已经有女朋友了。
But I've got this girlfriend.
我今晚就向她求婚。
And I'm gonna ask her to marry me tonight.
哦!
Aw!
——恭喜你。——谢谢!
- Congratulations. - Thanks!
但他还不知道，我觉得他可能需要一个自己的朋友。
But he doesn't know that yet, and I just think maybe he needs a friend of his own.
那我觉得艾斯是个完美的…你觉得豚鼠怎么样?
Well, then I think Ace here would be the perfect... How do you feel about guinea pigs?
打烊后我再来找你们。
I'll come back for all of you guys after closing.
保持强劲。
Stay strong.
好了。
There we go.
天啊，好痛。
Oh, man, that hurt.
是的。这也伤害了我。
Yes. And that hurt me as well.
因为我和普通的狗狗一样能感觉到疼痛。
Due to the fact that I feel pain as any ordinary canine would.
啊哈。总之，我正在越狱，所以你能不能…?
Uh-huh. Anyway, I'm kind of in the middle of a prison break, so could you please...?
越狱吗?
Prison break?
给我站住，停止你的非法活动，我从没见过的狗。
Stop right there and cease your unlawful activities, dog I've never met.
你到底在说什么，伙计?
The heck are you talking about, man?
你就是刚才跟在我后面的那条狗。
You the same dog that was literally just behind me.
不可能的。那只狗戴眼镜。
Impossible. That dog wore glasses.
现在投降吧，我不想伤害你。
Now surrender, I don't want to hurt you.
好吧，你想去那里吗。
Oh, okay, so you wanna take it there.
你想扔爪子，那好。
You wanna throw paws, then fine.
但我得提醒你，我有八分之一的鲍克瑟血统。
But I should warn you, I'm one-eighth Boxer.
和7/8的吉娃娃。
And seven-eighths Chihuahua.
吉娃娃犬是恶性。
Chihuahuas are vicious.
把这。拿一点这个。
Take that. Take a little bit of this.
敲一下，我就放你出来。
Tap out, and I'll let you out.
雷声来了!
Here come the thunder!
你会成功的!啊!
You're gonna get it! Ahhh!
哦,男人。我感到一阵疼痛。是啊，我得下跪。
Oh, man. I'm getting a stitch. Yeah, I gotta take a knee.
如果我没缝好这针，我就能让你如愿以偿了。
Oh, if I didn't get this stitch, I had you where I wanted you.
香蕉!让我……给我一根香蕉!快点!
Banana! Get me... Get me a banana! Hurry up!
这是寒冷的,男人。
That's cold, man.
哦!你真是一缕阳光啊?
Aw! Aren't you a little ray of sunshine?
什么?
What?
哦,Krypto。
Oh, Krypto.
你觉得自己很了不起，是吧，超级狗?
Oh, you think you're so great, don't you, Super dog?
你以为你的便便不臭。
You think your dookie don't stink.
我的便便不臭。
My dookie doesn't stink.
等等，等等，暂停。你是认真的吗，现在?
Wait, wait, time out. Are you serious, right now?
是的，它闻起来像檀香。
Yep, it actually smells like sandalwood.
说实话，这是一种边缘性的芳香疗法。
It's borderline aromatherapy, if I'm being honest.
哇!哇!
Whoa! Whoa!
你不正常，伙计。
You ain't normal, man.
是啊，至少我有主人了。
Yeah, well, at least I have an owner.
你不能拥有我。我是一只野生动物。
You can't own me. I'm a wild animal.
完全正确。那我们把你放回笼子里吧。
Exactly. So, let's get you back in the cage.
超人可能想我了。
Supes is probably missing me.
想?
Missing?
那家伙把你绑在停车标志上然后去收容所给你买了个新朋友好让你给他点空间。
The dude tied you up to the stop sign and went into that shelter to buy you a new friend so that you'd give him some space.
明白了。
Gotcha.
超人永远不会那样做。
Superman would never do that.
好吧，它现在真的正在发生。
Well, it's literally happening right now.
我很高兴那个新朋友不是我。
I'm just glad that that new friend ain't me.
放松,卡尔。
Easy, Carl.
别装得好像你不认识我似的。
Stop acting like you don't know me.
不错的尝试,胡迪尼。
Nice try, Houdini.
你说过你会回来找我们的
Well, you did say you'd come back for us.
哦,采用时间。
Ooh, adoption time.
我们总有一个人可以依偎在一起。
One of us is gonna get someone to snuggle with.
是啊，别抱太大希望。
Yeah, don't get your hopes up.
他们总是挑…给你，宝贝。
They always pick the... Here you go, baby.
哇!第一天。
Wow! First day.
成为一个救援动物是容易和有趣的!
Being a rescue animal is easy and fun!
嘿。下次你一定会抓到他们的。
Hey. You'll get 'em next time.
是的。下一个时间。
Yeah. Next time.
真不敢相信那个收容所的混蛋说我不正常。
I can't believe that shelter punk said I wasn't normal.
我是一只完全正常的狗。
I'm a totally normal dog.
超人也不可能在里面帮我找朋友。
And no way Superman was in there looking for a friend for me.
我不需要朋友
♪ I don't need a friend ♪
♬超人是我的朋友
♪ Supes is my friend ♪
♬我唯一的朋友是超人
♪ My only friend is Superman ♪
嗯。
Hmm.
那是什么?
What's that?
有人把流星拖向城市?
Someone is dragging a meteor toward the city?
卢梭。
Luthor.
你好,漂亮。
Hello, gorgeous.
我多么渴望你能进入我的太阳系啊。
Oh, how I have longed for you to enter my solar system.
这是一个摇滚。
It's a rock.
那块石头，梅西，百分之百是橙色氪石。
That rock, Mercy, is 100% orange kryptonite.
酷。另一个引火上身。
Cool. Another kryptonite scheme.
不，这次不一样!
No, this is different!
绿色氪石会夺走超人的能力，而橙色氪石会给我超能力。
Green kryptonite takes away Superman's powers, but orange kryptonite Will give me superpowers.
比如，隐身，激光眼，或者用力扔扑克牌。
You know, like, uh, invisibility or, uh, laser-eyes, or throwing playing cards really hard.
我终于要比那个愚蠢的…你不是在说我吧?
I'm finally gonna be stronger than that stupid... You're not talking about me, are you?
我想他也在说我。
Yeah, I think he was talking about me, too.
这是尴尬的。
That's awkward.
超人。
Superman.
我还以为你和你那杂种会早点来呢。
I'd expected you and that mutt of yours much sooner.
我需要你放开那颗流星，莱科斯。
I'm gonna need you to let go of that meteor, Lex.
很乐意。
Gladly.
Krypto,取回!
Krypto, fetch!
那只狗是个英雄!
That dog's a hero!
Krypto !
Krypto!
好狗。
Good dog.
让我们把这东西放回它该去的地方。
Let's put this thing back in space where it belongs.
女士。婴儿。
Ma'am. Baby.
让我们看看你现在能不能抓住它。
Let's see if you can catch it now.
啊!
Ah!
你忘了一件事，莱克斯。
You forgot one thing, Lex.
不像你，我有朋友。
Unlike you, I have friends.
谢谢你把你那愚蠢的邪恶总部建在河边。
Thanks for building your stupid evil headquarters on the river.
对水工来说非常方便。
Very convenient for the water guy.
我潜水侠!
I'm Aquaman!
哦,太棒了。这些jabronies。
Oh, great. These jabronies.
有人给技术支持打电话了吗?
Uh, did somebody call tech support?
你试过关机再开机吗?
Have you tried turning it off and on again?
谢谢你,朋友。
Thanks, buddy.
好友吗?不，这些人最多是工作上的朋友。
Buddy? No, these people are work friends at best.
请系好安全带。
Please fasten your safety belts.
他们是看不见的。
They are invisible.
没错，这些东西都不是隐形的。
Yeah, none of this stuff is invisible.
它真的更透明了。
It's really more transparent.
嗯?
Hmm?
我喜欢你的激光装置。
I like your laser thing.
但是绿色看起来更好。
But it looks better in green.
是的。
Yeah.
LexCorp公司的权力诉讼开始了。
LexCorp power suit engaged.
温暖的激活。
Seat warmer activated.
我花过的最好的十亿美元。
Best billion I ever spent.
我只需要一小块。
All I need is one little piece.
上帝保佑你的小心脏。
Aw, bless your little heart.
你以为你会抢先一步吗?
Did you think you were gonna get to it first?
谢谢你！
Thank you.
我成为了我一直想成为的人。
I am what I was always meant to become.
嗯?这是什么?
Huh? What is this?
但我应该有超能力的!
But I'm supposed to have superpowers!
他们高估了。
They're overrated.
好男孩,Krypto。
Good boy, Krypto.
谁是好孩子?谁是好孩子?
Who's a good boy? Who's a good boy?
你是我的超级狗狗吗?是吗?
Are you my super dog go? Are you?
哦!的舌头。
Oh! In the tongue.
谁是好孩子?谁是好孩子?
Who's a good boy? Who's a good boy?
我想念我的父母。
I miss my parents.
是谁把氪星石扔回太空的?
Who threw that kryptonite back into space?
你好,漂亮。
Hello, gorgeous.
我是多么渴望你能进入我的太阳系啊。
Oh, how I've longed for you to enter my solar system.
你赢了这一轮，生菜。
You win this round, lettuce.
伙计们，怎么了?
Guys, what's going on?
没什么,PB。
Nothing, PB.
只是你们说疯狂的计划结果却疯狂的好。
Just the plan that you all called crazy turns out to be crazy good.
我回到实验室的时候，有个人类。
You see, when I was back in the lab, there was this human.
他邪恶，虐待狂，性感。
He was evil, sadistic, hot.
我们是两位寻找终极力量的科学家。
And together we were two scientists searching for ultimate power.
当然，在这个过程中也有失误。
Of course, there were missteps along the way.
红色氪石让我的头发都掉光了。
The red kryptonite made my hair fall out.
幸运的是，我的骨骼结构可以把它拉下来。
Luckily, I had the bone structure to pull it off.
紫色给我带来了令人不安的生动的梦。
Purple gave me uncomfortably vivid dreams.
但橙色…我们知道橘子会不一样。
But the orange... we knew the orange would be different.
我们有一个计划。
And we had a plan.
直到超级狗克瑞普来毁了它。
Until Krypto the Super dog had to come and ruin it.
愚蠢的名字。以他的星球命名。哦,真正的创新。
Stupid name. Named after his planet. Oh, real creative.
谢谢,Krypto !
Thanks, Krypto!
我要回家了，儿子!
I'm coming home, son!
嗯?你到底在干什么?
Huh? What the heck are you doing?
我要把你从这个可怕的动物实验室里解救出来。
I'm freeing you from this horrible animal testing lab.
不!这是我的家!
No! This is my home!
现在这就是你的新家。
And now this is your new home.
——欢迎你。-你在说什么?
- You're welcome. - What are you talking about?
哦，你是最可爱的!
Oh, you're the sweetest!
放掉我,姑娘!
Unhand me, wench!
所以我在这个令人不安的小屋里等待时机，准备着。
So I bided my time in this disturbing hovel, preparing.
因为我发现了连莱科斯都做不到的事。
Because I'd figured out something that even Lex couldn't.
橙色氪石对人不起作用。
Orange kryptonite doesn't work on people.
它只对宠物有效。
It only works on pets.
露露，你还好吗?
Uh, Lulu, are you okay?
我很好，猪。
Oh, I'm more than okay, pig.
我成为了我一直想成为的人。
I am what I was always meant to become.
露露,嘿。什么?带我们一起走，好吗?
Lulu, hey. What? Take us with you, okay?
我们收留动物，你知道，我们……我们要团结在一起，对吧?团结。
Us shelter animals, you know, we... we gotta stick together, right? Solidarity.
哦，艾斯，对不起。
Oh, Ace, I'm sorry.
我现在真的没有时间照顾宠物!
I don't really have time in my life right now to take care of a pet!
露露,等等!
Lulu, wait!
不要把我们留在这里!
Do not leave us here!
别担心，我相信总有一天会有人收养你的。
Don't worry, I'm sure someone wonderful will adopt you any day.
关于我的什么?
What about me?
哦,胡须。
Oh, Whiskers.
当然。我不是怪物。
Of course. I'm not a monster.
想念你的。爱你。玩得开心。
Miss you. Love you. Have fun.
等等,PB。我来救我们出去。
Hold on, PB. I'mma get us out.
我闻到培根!
I smell bacon!
我为什么流口水?
Why is my mouth watering?
这里有太多东西需要整理。
There's so much to unpack here.
伙计们,我小!
Guys, I'm small!
刚才发生了什么?
What just happened?
不，说真的，刚刚发生了什么?我看不到。
No, seriously, what just happened? I can't see.
橙色氪石也给了我超能力。
The orange kryptonite gave me powers, too.
这是我的起源故事。
This is my origin story.
我叔叔甚至不用死。
And my uncle didn't even have to die.
嗯，那太好了。
Uh, yeah, that's great.
但这对你的老朋友艾斯来说可不太好。
But it ain't lookin' too good for your old pal Ace.
正确的。神奇猪，还在想名字，还在想。
Right. Wonder Pig, still working on the name, is on it.
哦。
Uh-oh.
——王牌,不!——王牌!
- Ace, no! - Ace!
我现在应该死了才对，对吧?
I should be a lot more dead right now, right?
哦,我的天啊。
Oh, my gosh.
橙色氪星石也给了你超能力!
The orange kryptonite gave you powers, too!
你是超级强!
You're super strong!
你的尾巴现在是火做的。
And your tail is now made of fire.
我很抱歉。我的什么是谁?
I'm sorry. My what is who?
我的尾巴!啊，放开我的……哦,我的尾巴…我的尾巴着火了!
My tail! Ah, let go of my... Oh, my tail... My tail on fire!
我的尾巴着火了!
I got my tail on fire!
王牌,这很好。看到了吗?
Ace, it's fine. See?
嗯?
Huh?
你是无敌的。
You're invulnerable.
我可以把自己缩小到…
And I can shrink myself down to the size of an...
啊!
Ah!
还在解决问题。我什么都没看见。
Still working out the kinks. I didn't see anything.
你去找奇普，我去找默特。
You go get Chip, I'll get Mert.
用你的脸，生菜。
In your face, lettuce.
哦,太棒了。
Oh, great.
我是唯一一个没有得到超能力的人…
I'm the only one who didn't get any super...
大都市97.2……光滑的爵士乐。
Metropolis 97.2... ...smooth jazz.
-来吧，我们离开这里。——正确的。
- Come on, let's get outta here. - Right.
更新。
Update.
我现在快了，但我还是看不见。
I'm fast now, but I still can't see.
嗯。我们开始吧。
Uh-uh. Here we go.
好的。周四晚上看电视。
All right. Thursday night TV night.
该和我兄弟在大都会看我最喜欢的节目了。嗯?
Time for my favorite show with my bro in Metropo. Huh?
♬我是超人♬
♪ I am Superman ♪
♬我可以做任何…♪
♪ And I can do any... ♪
嗯?什么……?
Huh? What the...?
让我来解决这个问题。
Let me just iron that out.
他们应该叫我钢铁侠。不。
They should call me Iron Man. No.
看看你，光鲜亮丽。
Well, look at you, all spiffy.
在英国烘焙大赛上打扮得很漂亮。
Pretty dressed up for the British Bake Off.
但是你知道吗?它是有意义的。
But you know what? It makes sense.
这是本季的最后一集。
This is the season finale.
你有约会?
You have a date?
“烘焙之夜”?
On Bake Off night?
哦!嘿，小家伙。
Aw! Hey there, little fella.
不。
Nah.
嘿,露易丝。哦!
Hey, Lois. Oh!
哦。听着,伙计,我…今天是馅饼周。
Oh. Listen, buddy, I... It is pie week.
你的选择。她或我。
Your choice. Her or me.
你怎么了?
What's gotten into you?
坏狗。
Bad dog.
你刚才叫我什么?
What did you just call me?
这太过分了，伙计。我是说，如果你想…我们等我回家再谈。
That is way out of line, fella. I mean, if you want... We'll talk about this when I get home.
我太想你了!
I've missed you so much!
你又把"挤压布鲁斯"忘在走廊了。
You left Squeezy Bruce in the hallway again.
很好。
Fine.
我一个人看着面包皮变脆。
I'll watch the crusts crisp alone.
坏老板!
Bad owner!
下面也很湿。
It's quite wet right underneath as well.
底部有点湿。
Slightly soggy bottom there.
♬因为现在我们有了嫌隙♬
♪ 'Cause baby now we got bad blood ♪
♬你知道这曾经是疯狂的爱
♪ You know it used to be mad love ♪
嗯?
Huh?
卡尔·艾尔，乔·艾尔的儿子，我是露露，辛纳蒙的女儿，你要跪在我面前。
Kal-El, son of Jor-El, I am Lulu, daughter of Cinnamon, and you will kneel before me.
等一下。
Wait a minute.
你不是收容所的仓鼠吗?
Aren't you the hamster from the shelter?
我是小白鼠，我说跪下!
I am a guinea pig, and I said kneel!
看，看我从旧实验室找到了什么。
Well, lookie-lookie what I got from the old lab.
帮助,Krypto……-♪我们有问题♪-♪我们有问题♪
Help, Krypto... - ♪ We got problems ♪ - ♪ We got problems ♪
♬我不认为我们能解决……♪
♪ And I don't think we can solve... ♪
我想我们能解决
♪ Think we can solve them ♪
你真应该让我更难找到你。
You really should have made it harder to find you.
那副眼镜骗不了任何人。
Those glasses aren't fooling anyone.
可能会留胡子，但不会戴眼镜。
Moustache maybe, but not glasses.
哇!
Whoa!
为什么约会之夜总是这样?
Why does this always happen on date night?
这里是正义联盟的紧急热线。
You've reached the Justice League emergency line.
地球一号，请按1。
For Earth-One, press one.
地球二号，请按2。
For Earth-Two, press two.
为地球三…天啊，看起来很疼啊。
For Earth-Three... Oh, man, that looked like it hurt.
我希望如此。
I hope it did.
哇，你还在努力。
Wow, look at you still trying.
勇敢的。
Plucky.
很好,然后。妈妈喜欢大打出手。
Fine, then. Mama likes a good fight.
你烘焙总是有原因的。
You always bake for a reason.
所以，你尽你所能做到最好。
So, you make it the best you can.
你用爱来创造它。
And you make it with love.
投降。我不想伤害你。
Surrender. I don't wanna hurt you.
不,不,不。
No, no, no.
一个小的建议。
A little advice.
永远不要测试豚鼠。好吗?
Never test a guinea pig. Okay?
我不敢相信他真的跟她走了。
I can't believe he really left with her.
我说话的时候，他们可能正在外面玩捉迷藏。
They're probably out there playing fetch together as I speak.
哦，他给我留下了奶酪!
Ooh, he left me cheese!
我没法一直生他的气。
Ah, I can't stay mad at the guy.
的帮助。
Help.
超人吗?
Superman?
小狗，起来，走开!
Pup, up, and away!
你对他做了什么?
What have you done to him?
我看到有人找到了他的药。
I see someone found his medicine.
一小块绿色氪星石巧妙地藏在一大块加尔斯堡石里。
A tiny shard of green kryptonite cleverly concealed in a hunk of Jarlsberg.
他们总是把它放在奶酪里。
They always put it in the cheese.
你把我从莱科斯身边带走，所以现在我要把超人从你身边带走。
You took me away from Lex, so now I'm taking Superman away from you.
别担心，这只是我邪恶计划的第一步。
Oh, uh, don't worry, this is only step one of my evil plan.
有更多的。
There's more.
不。
No.
必须保护超级…
Must protect Super...
超人!
Superman!
我必须找到……
I have to find...
嗯?
Huh?
的父亲。
Father.
是的，是我，狗-艾尔。
Yes, it is I, Dog-El.
当你还是只小狗的时候，我把我所有的知识都记录在你的项圈里。
When you were just a puppy, I recorded all my knowledge in your collar.
我知道。你过去一直帮我，现在我真的很需要你。
I know. You've always helped me in the past, and I could really use you now.
是的，是我，狗-艾尔。
Yes, it is I, Dog-El.
我们真的需要一个跳过介绍按钮。
We really need a skip-intro button.
告诉我，我的儿子。有什么问题吗?
Talk to me, my son. What seems to be the problem?
超人。他被抓获。
Superman. He's been captured.
嗯。
Hmm.
我很抱歉。我知道你离我有多近。
I'm sorry. I know how close you are.
是的，我是说，我们是。
Yeah, I mean, we were.
你总不能坐在那儿伤心吧。
Well, you just can't sit there feeling sad.
你得去救他。
You have to go rescue him.
你是对的。
You're right.
我会救超人，等我救了他，他就会意识到我是他唯一需要的朋友。
I'll save Superman, and when I do, he'll realize that I'm the only friend he ever needs.
嗯…那不是我…但如果我没有超能力我怎么能成为英雄呢?
Uh... That's not exactly what I... But how am I supposed to be a hero when I don't have my powers?
不是超能力让你成为英雄的，克瑞普。
It's not superpowers that make you a hero, Krypto.
那不是你的问题。
That's not your problem.
那是什么?
Then what is it?
-你的问题是你自己。——你……我吗?你什么意思，我?父亲吗?
- Your problem is you. - You... Me? What do you mean, me? Father?
啊哈!
A-ha!
那一定是可恶的啮齿动物。
That must be the vile rodent.
别担心，超人，不救你我不会休息的。
Don't worry, Superman, I won't rest until I rescue you.
这是非常安静的。
This is very restful.
是的。
Yes.
哎呦。
Whoops.
我们得努力解决这个问题。
We're gonna have to work on that.
我从来不知道星星还能这么美，而且有这么多星星。
I never knew the stars could be this beautiful, and there's so many of them.
看,有一个。哦，还有一个。
Look, there's one. Oh, there's another one.
看，还有一个。
Look, there's one, too.
嗯!这些星星都是垃圾。等我们到了农场。
Eh! These stars are crap. Wait till we get to the farm.
是的。农场里的一切都好。
Yeah. Everything's better at the farm.
哦!哦,是的。
Oh! Oh, yeah.
嗯,是的,关于…关于农场。
Um, yeah, about... about the farm.
看到的,理解这一点。
See, understand this.
总是有一个字面上的解释，然后…然后更…她在哪里呢?在哪里…?
There's always a literal interpretation and then... and then a more... Where is she? Where...?
在哪里…?
Where...?
好的。在那里……她在哪里呢?
Okay. Where... Where is she?
好的。她在哪里呢?
Okay. Where is she?
啊。
Ugh.
我很抱歉。我很抱歉。
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
我以前从没真正跑过步。
I've, uh, I've never really run before.
我…我通常会“小狗，爬起来，走开。”
I... I usually "Pup, up, and away."
你还好吗?
Are you okay?
我没事，我没事。
I'm fine, I'm fine.
我只是，被车撞了一下。
I was just, uh, hit by a car a little.
你永远不会忘记你的第一次。
You never forget your first time.
等等，我在哪儿见过你?
Wait a minute, where do I know you from?
我不能把爪子放在上面。
I can't put my paw on it.
她在哪里呢?
Where is she?
哇。我看到的超能力是你的吗?
Whoa. So, the powers I saw were yours?
你们这些流氓可以帮我。
You hooligans can help me.
快点，时间不多了。我们必须拯救超人。
Hurry, there isn't much time. We have to save Superman.
超人吗?
Superman?
哦,当然!你就是那个害我回监狱的超级蠢蛋。
Oh, of course! You're that super dork who got me thrown back in the slammer.
是什么?之道?胖子吗?你叫什么名字?
What was it? Creepo? Crisco? What's your name?
不。是超级狗氪星!
No. It's Krypto the Super dog!
哦!
Oh!
看来我们现在都是超级英雄了。
Well, it looks like we're both super now.
你知道吗，我还欠你一顿。
You know, I still owe you a whuppin'.
——Hi-yah !——噢!
- Hi-yah! - Ow!
那是我的好眼睛。
That was my good eye.
现在,等待。这本该是一场公平的战斗。
Now, wait. It was supposed to be a fair fight.
你为什么不用从耳朵里冒出来的冷热堵住我?
Why didn't you block me with some freeze heat that was coming out your ears or something?
因为,我…我…我没有超能力了。
Because, I... I... I don't have my powers.
什么?
What?
我说我已经没有超能力了。
I said I don't have my powers anymore.
丫……吗?
Did ya...?
你没有能力了?
You don't have your powers?
是啊，就是这样。
Yeah, that's what's going on.
你现在只是想利用我们，因为你一个人应付不了。
You're just trying to use us now, because you can't handle it on your own.
听着，我知道这些能力对你来说很陌生，但是当一个人拥有足够的能力... ...他们有一定的责任使用这种权力来…
Look, I know these powers are new to you, but when one has an abundance of power... ...they have a certain duty to use that power to...
对不起。你刚才说什么?
Sorry. You were sayin' somethin'?
我在做鼓舞人心的英雄演讲。
I was making an inspiring hero speech.
你喝了多少?
How much did you have to drink?
我有两个抽水马桶和一个坐浴盆。
I had two toilet bowls and a bidet.
还有个坐浴盆，这太疯狂了。
A bidet, too, which is, which is crazy.
我都不知道还有这种东西。
I didn't even know that was a thing.
但它就像个狗饮水器。
But it's like a dog water fountain.
你恶心的动物。
You disgusting animal.
收拾行李，我们出发。
Pack, let's roll out.
我再也见不到你了，缉毒警肯特。
I'll see you never, Narc Kent.
不!我最好的朋友有危险，你得帮我。
No! My best friend is in danger, and you have to help me.
抱歉，我们有其他安排。
Sorry, we got other plans.
祝你好运。我们要去农场。
Good luck with your danger. We're going to the farm.
哦,耶!生菜树木,宝贝!
Oh, yeah! Lettuce trees, baby!
“莴苣树”?这个农场叫什么?
"Lettuce trees"? What's this farm called?
农场北部。
The farm upstate.
听起来的。
That sounds made-up.
噢,是吗?你怎么知道?
Oh, yeah? Well, how would you know?
我在农场长大。在一个叫史摩维尔的小镇。
I grew up on a farm. In a town called Smallville.
这听起来像是瞎编的。
Now that sounds made-up.
那么，这个所谓的农场在哪里?
So, which way is this so-called farm?
它的北部。
Well, it's upstate.
所以,这……这意味着它的…这是明显的。
So, that... that means it's... it's up, obviously.
好的。他不会告诉你…我能占用你一点时间吗?
Okay. He's not telling you the... Can I steal you for a sec?
农场的事你撒谎了，对吧?
You lied about the farm, didn't you?
大的时间。我得给他们一些希望。
Big time. Look, I had to give them some hope.
-那里有一个。-没人会收养我们的
- There's one there. - No one was ever gonna adopt us.
也有一个。
There's one, too.
所以，我答应他们这将是他们的新家。
So, I promised them it would be their new home.
我很乐意带你和你的朋友们去我的农场。
You know, I'd be happy to take you and your friends to my farm.
如果你帮我救超人。
If you help me save Superman.
等一下。这是敲诈吗?你在勒索我吗?
Wait a minute. Is this blackmail? Are you blackmailing me?
不。我只是想让你做点事，作为回报我不会泄露有害信息。
No. I'm just asking you for something, which I will reward you for by not revealing damaging information.
这就是勒索的真正含义。
That is literally the definition of blackmail.
好吧。我们会帮你找回你的蠢主人。
Fine. We'll help you get your dumb owner back.
你有一个超级团队。
You got yourself a super team.
刚才是不是有人说超级战队?
Did someone just say super team?
耶。等待我的命运。
Yay. My destiny awaits.
可怕的恶棍，致命的刺客，我来招募你们进行一场凶残的野蛮围攻!
Terrifying villains, deadly assassins, I have come to recruit you for a siege of murderous savagery!
我的伙伴，皮货商，豚鼠。
My fellow, furrier, guinea pigs.
我找到你是因为你是顶级掠食者。
I have sought you out because you are apex predators.
人在神!
Gods amongst men!
好,看。猪对猪，我需要你的帮助因为我的主人陷入了困境。
Okay, look. Pig to pig, I need your help because my owner has gotten himself into a bit of a pickle.
在正义联盟的阻挠下，莱克斯·卢瑟身陷囹圄。
Thwarted by the Justice League, Lex Luthor now finds himself behind bars.
我要把你们都灭了!
I'll destroy you all!
那是我最好的朋友。
That's my best friend.
和导师。最好的朋友和导师。
And mentor. Best friend and mentor.
斯特瑞克岛是为关押可怕的超能力罪犯而建造的，是世界上最无法逃脱的监狱。
Built to house fearsome super powered criminals, Stryker's Island is the world's most inescapable prison.
这就是你们这些笨蛋的用武之地。
Which is where you dorks come in.
如果我要把莱科斯从那个破地方救出来，我需要一支军队。
You see, if I'm gonna get Lex outta that dump, I'm gonna need an army.
其实，我觉得我们还是待在这里比较好。
Um, actually, I think we'd just rather stay here.
是啊，我们有暑假，可以尽情喝水。
Yeah, I mean, we get summers off, all-you-can-drink water.
我们甚至每分钟都有西班牙语课。
We even have Spanish class every miercoles.
哦，你什么都没有……直到你从冰冷的权力的钢吸管中舔过。
Oh, you have nothing... until you've licked from the cold steel straw of power.
没有那么快。
Not so fast.
露易丝·莱恩跟我们提过你，仓鼠。
Lois Lane told us all about you, hamster.
仓鼠吗?仓鼠是……是沙包!
Hamster? A hamster is a... is a hacky sack!
仓鼠是一种午餐吃太多的老鼠!
A hamster is a mouse that had too much for lunch!
我们是小白鼠，等我们搞定你，老兄，你就知道了。
We are guinea pigs and when we're through with you, buster, you'll know it.
嗯。
Hmm.
这是怎么呢那是你进攻的信号。
What's going on? That was your cue to attack.
嗯…哦,对不起。我…我在等他先走。
Uh... Oh, sorry. I... I was waiting for him to go first.
但如果我先走，你的火会融化我的冰，所以也许…应该让空姐先来?
Yeah, but if I went first, your fire would melt my ice, so maybe the... the wing lady should go first?
我有名字。
I have a name.
但之后我会点燃她的翅膀，我想我们都不希望那样。
But then I'd set her wings on fire, and I don't think any of us want that.
你不会想在鸡翅上加冰的。
Well, you don't want ice on wings.
——为什么?——他们……它堵塞了羽毛。
- Why? - They... It clogs the feathers.
只是让他!
Just get him!
哇!这是有趣的。
Whoo! That was fun.
现在，我们去救莱科斯。
Now then, let's go free Lex.
嗯?
Huh?
这事到此为止，妹妹。
This ends now, sister.
你在我的真理套索里。
I have you in my Lasso of Truth.
你想知道真相?
Oh, you want the truth?
这双靴子有点多。
The boots are a bit much.
这真的是找到超人的最好方法吗?
Is this really the best way to find Superman?
因为对我来说，这太恶心了。
Because to me, this just seems gross.
你说恶心是什么意思?
What do you mean, gross?
嗅东西是作为一只狗最大的乐趣之一。
Smelling stuff is one of the greatest joys of being a dog.
仅次于舔你身体的任何部位。
Next to licking any part of your body.
我是说，我一直在舔自己。
I mean, I lick myself all the time.
这就解释了他的呼吸。
Well, that explains the breath.
你想找到露露，救出发胶队长，对吗?
You wanna find Lulu and rescue Captain Hair Gel, right?
我建议你开始闻。
Well, I suggest you start sniffing.
你知道人们常说，嗅觉是鼻子的视觉。
You know what they say, smell is the sight of the nose.
没人这么说。
No one says that.
他们应该。检查它。
Well, they should. Check it.
啊哈。
Uh-huh.
一只贵宾犬在这里流口水。
A poodle drooled right here.
有人往垃圾箱里扔了块好吃的披萨皮。
Someone threw a perfectly good pizza crust in that dumpster right there.
在那个角落……那边的那个角落……哦,不。见鬼。
And on that corner... That corner right there... Oh, no. Dang.
一只鸽子心碎了。我还能闻到伤痛的味道。
A pigeon got her heart broken. I can still smell the hurt.
她是个爱哭的人。
She was a heavy crier.
这是每只狗都有的超能力。
It's a superpower that every dog possesses.
即使是像你这样的怪人。
Even a wack one like you.
我不是怪人。
I'm not wack.
哦!
Oh!
那是创可贴吗?
Ooh, is that a band-aid?
——这是walk-o点。——What-oh-what ?
- It's walk-o'clock. - What-oh-what?
——什么都没有。——好的。
- Nothing. - Okay.
因为这听起来像是你和主人散步时得到的超级可爱的昵称。
Because it sounded like a super adorable nickname you got for your walks with your owner.
好吧，也许这是我以前和超人一起玩的时候。
All right, maybe this is when me and Supes used to hang out.
每天早上，从我还是只小狗的时候。
Every morning, since I was a puppy.
哦!也许你没有超人，但至少你有我们。
Aw! Well, you might not have your Superman, but at least you have us.
一个超级团队!
A whole super team!
强大的呼噜声!
The Mighty Oink!
Squirrelverine。
Squirrelverine.
Droolo。
Droolo.
严重吗?Droolo吗?
Seriously? Droolo?
等等，轮子上的贝壳在哪里?壳吗?
And wait, where's Shell-on-wheels? Shell?
怎么了，亲爱的?
What's happenin', sweet cheeks?
啊，我明白了。坚强，沉默的类型。
Ah, I get it. The strong, silent type.
谁需要的话?
Who needs words?
我真希望我还有超能力。
Man, I wish I still had my powers.
是啊，他们到底怎么了?
Yeah, what happened to them anyway?
我吃了一些绿色的氪石。
I ate some green kryptonite.
氪星人唯一的弱点。
A Kryptonian's only weakness.
你为什么要吃掉你的弱点，你个笨蛋?
Why would you eat your weakness, you dum-dum?
它在一些奶酪里。
It was in some cheese.
狗唯一的弱点。
A dog's only weakness.
我曾经吃过一只玩具恐龙。
Well, I ate a toy dinosaur once.
如果我们不这么做，我想说在那东西消失之前你大概还有整整两天。
If we're goin' off that, I'd say you probably got a solid two days until that thing passes.
除非是剑龙，然后你就祈祷。
Unless it's a stegosaurus, and then you just pray.
你们看!
You guys, look!
好吧，神奇女侠会阻止她。
M'kay, Wonder Woman will stop her.
女神,不!
Goddess, no!
嗯…
Um...
听起来像是骨头断了。
That sounded like a bone breaking.
真的是这样吗?
Is that even how it works?
我想这取决于我们。
I guess it's down to us.
谁准备好去救我最好的朋友了?
Who's ready to go save my best friend?
你想让我们跟她打?
You want us to fight her?
她刚干掉了整个正义联盟!
She just took out the whole Justice League!
它们都有可对立的拇指。
And they all have opposable thumbs.
我死后你要记得我，法布里齐奥。
Remember me when I'm gone, Fabrizio.
伙计,放松。我们会好起来的。
Guys, relax. We'll be fine.
他们为什么这么生气?
Why are they so mad?
你看到了什么?完全好了。
You see? Totally fine.
现在，让我们逞英雄吧。
Now, let's hero up.
好了，队员们，你们的数据如何?
All right, team, what are your stats?
比如，我的超能力包括热视觉，冻结呼吸…别忘了还有太阳能爪拳。
Like, my powers include heat vision, freeze breath... And don't forget the Solar Paw Punch.
那是什么?
What is that?
是果汁盒口味的吗?
Is that like a juice box flavor or something?
不，这是氪星最强大的招数。
No, it's Krypto's most powerful move.
它要求他直接飞向太阳，吸收太阳的致命辐射，把自己变成一个狗形的热能事件。
It requires him to fly directly to the sun and absorb its deadly radiation, turning himself into a dog-shaped thermal energy event.
连超人自己都没试过。
Not even Superman himself has tried it.
因为他没有爪子?
Because he doesn't have paws?
因为这不是你能挽回的事情。
Because it's not something you come back from.
这一拳造成了冲击波，不仅杀死了被击中的恶棍，还杀死了扔出这一拳的英雄。
The punch causes a blast which takes out not only the villain who gets hit with the blow, but the hero who throws it.
听起来是一种可怕的力量。
Sounds like a terrible power.
听起来倒是挺不错的果汁盒。
Does sound like a good juice box, though.
我会喝果汁盒。
I would drink the juice box.
好的,足够的混乱。谢谢你！我们得走了……我的天哪!
Okay, enough mayhem. Thank you. We gotta go... My goodness!
看谁还活着!
Look who's alive!
我们来纠正一下这个小疏忽，好吗?
Well, let's correct that little oversight, shall we?
艾斯，展开犬齿护盾。
Ace, deploy canine shield.
狗是什么?
What is a canine...?
逃避!
Evade!
良好的屏蔽。
Excellent shielding.
这似乎非常痛苦。
That seemed incredibly painful.
有人想转换能量吗?
Anybody wanna switch powers?
你了,猪。
You're up, pig.
好了，PB，往大了想!
Okay, PB, think big!
松鼠，把灯点亮。
Squirrel, light 'em up.
不,不,不。我不能。
No, no, no. I can't.
你当然可以。
Of course you can.
我是说，能发生的最坏的情况是什么?
I mean, what's the worst that could happen?
我可能会伤害别人。或者他们会伤害我。
I could hurt someone. Or they could hurt me.
也许我被冻成这样是最糟糕的事。
Or maybe me freezing like this is the worst thing.
乌龟，用你的速度抓住他们…在上面。
Turtle, use your speed and get them... On it.
我在哪里?
Where the am I?
你们是糟糕的超级英雄。
You guys are terrible superheroes.
我不明白你为什么不明白。
I don't understand why you're not getting this.
是啊，我们之间有很多事你都不了解，傻瓜。
Yeah, well, there's a lot that you don't understand about us, you fool.
如果你注意…嗯?
Maybe if you paid attention to... Huh?
-我注意听了——帮助。
- Oh, I'm paying attention. - Help.
One-hundo百分比的注意。
One-hundo percent attention.
他的腹肌又厚又肿
So thick and swole, his abs.
他的腹肌。
His abs.
对一只没有超能力的狗来说这是很危险的举动。
Risky move for a dog with no powers.
有些人会说英勇。
Some would say heroic.
我会说蠢。
I would say dumb.
超人在哪里?
Where is Superman?
我不会说。
I'm not telling.
经典的邪恶。莱科斯会很自豪的。
Classic evil. Lex would be so proud.
这真的是因为莱科斯·卢瑟吗
This is really about Lex Luthor?
难道你不明白吗?他在考验你。
Don't you understand? He was testing on you.
我们是同事。我们一起是科学家。
We were colleagues. We were scientists together.
你是小白鼠。你的头发掉了。
You were the guinea pig. Your hair fell out.
是的。就像他一样。Lex需要我。
Yeah. Just like his did. Lex needed me.
这比你的超人强多了。
That's more than I can say for your Superman.
超人需要我。他……他需要我。
Superman needed me. He... he needs me.
是吗?
Does he?
因为我很确定他会从他的…未婚妻。
Because I'm pretty sure he's gonna get everything he needs from his... fiancee.
哦,不。
Oh, no.
你不知道他们要结婚了。
You didn't know they were getting married.
我真的很抱歉，因为从我这里听到这些一定很痛苦。
I really am sorry, 'cause this must be so painful to have to hear this from me.
不。你就是在说谎。
No. You're lying.
我是吗?嗯。
Am I? Huh.
那我干掉他的那晚为什么他的内裤里会掉出这个小玩意?
Well, then why did this little bauble fall out of his Underoos the night I took him down?
看它。
Look at it.
切口很好，但清晰度很模糊。
The cut's fine but the clarity is murky as heck.
面对现实吧，神奇狗，你来得太晚了。
Face it, Wonder Mutt, you're too late.
你儿子要结婚了。这意味着……再见,狗。
Your boy's getting hitched. And that means... Bye-bye, dog.
但别担心，如果超人的生活中没有你的空间了，我相信你可以，在司法大厅里睡一觉。
But don't worry, if Superman doesn't have room in his life for you anymore, I'm sure you can, uh, crash at the Hall of Justice.
哇!她把那条狗扔得很远。
Wow! She threw that dog real far.
你知道有趣的是什么吗?当我看到橙色氪星石给你超能力的时候我还很担心，但后来我想起来了，你就是你。
You know what's funny? For a minute, I was worried when I saw that the orange kryptonite gave you powers, but then I remembered, uh, you're you.
来吧，我们走，小猪们。
Come on, let's go, little piggies.
我怎么跟你说的?这不是比西班牙语课好吗?
What did I tell you? Isn't this better than Spanish class?
Si。
Si.
嘿,露易丝·莱恩。
Hey, Lois Lane.
见到你总是很高兴。
Always nice to see ya.
说话,Lex。我知道你是幕后主使。
Talk, Lex. I know you're behind this.
令人印象深刻的破坏，但不是我的工作。
Impressive destruction, but not my work.
你的名字就在怪物身上。
Your name is literally on the monster.
看来我的小宝贝长大了。
Looks like one of my little babies is all grown up.
这是令人毛骨悚然的。
That's creepy.
Lex泄漏。你对超人做了什么?
Spill it, Lex. What have you done with Superman?
无论超人在哪里，都与我，或我的公司LexCorp International无关。
Wherever Superman is, it's got nothing to do with me, or my company, LexCorp International.
嘿!别嚼巴塔朗了。
Hey! Stop chewing on that Batarang.
布鲁斯·韦恩为此花了很多钱，然后把它作为礼物送给我。
Bruce Wayne paid a lot of money for that, and then gave it to me as a present.
维克，你能解除他们的防御吗?
Vic, can you override their defenses?
当我被困在飞行模式时，我什么都做不了。
I can't do anything while they got me stuck in airplane mode.
那些关于外星人入侵的协议，一点都没有。
All those protocols for an alien invasion, nothing for little furballs.
这些四足陆地狂人犯了一个巨大的错误，和……哦,哇!
These quadrupedal land maniacs have made a giant mistake messing with the King of... Oh, whoa!
嘿,等等。那是鱼食吗?
Hey, hold on. Is that fish food?
哦，有人饿了。
Aw, someone was hungy.
莱科斯·卢瑟否认参与其中，但自称是"坏人小组"
Lex Luthor denies involvement, but is quote "team bad guy."
幸运的是，超人的狗是我们队的。
Luckily, Superman's dog is on our team.
Krypto吗?
Krypto?
当然是和超人亲热的狗狗。他会拯救我们。
Of course, Superman's dog he makes out with. He'll save us.
不。
No.
他没有超能力。
He doesn't have his powers.
但其他动物有。
But those other animals do.
…难道氪星人就不能和他们一起…拯救大都市?
And... and like, can't Krypto work with them to... to save Metropolis?
是的,。
Yeah, about that.
他不是最擅长对付其他动物的。
He's not the greatest with other animals.
他最好快点振作起来，不然雪貂就要统治世界了。
He better get it together soon, or those ferrets are gonna take over the world.
他没事吧?
Is he okay?
看起来他还有呼吸。
Looks like he's still breathing.
是的。他还活着
Yep. He's alive.
给钱吧,小子
Pay up, dog.
你赌我还活着吗?
You bet on if I was alive?
没有。我打赌如果你死了。
Nope. I bet on if you were dead.
我敢说你当时伤得很重。
I bet you were horribly maimed.
-多么有趣的游戏。——嘿!
- What a fun game. - Hey!
那，这到底是什么地方?
So, what, uh, what is this place anyway?
这是什么高级车管所吗?
Is this some type of fancy DMV?
你在开玩笑吧?这是司法大厅。
Are you kidding? It's the Hall of Justice.
这里是正义联盟出没的地方。
This is where the Justice League hangs out.
我打赌他们都是超级亲密的朋友，他们会互相试穿对方的衣服，吃非常有趣的零食，然后他们可能会告诉对方所有的事情。
I bet they're all super tight buds, and they, like, try on each other's clothes and then they eat, like, really fun snacks, and then they probably just tell each other everything.
是的。一切。
Yeah. Everything.
他看起来很伤心，很失败。
He seems sad and defeated.
所以，这是车管所。
So, it is a DMV.
也许我们应该有个人去跟他谈谈。
Maybe one of us should go talk to him.
没有它。
Not it.
艾斯，你总是知道该说什么。
Ace, you always know what to say.
请关注... ...隐形飞机。
Watch out for the... ...invisible jet.
我只想一个人待着。
I just want to be alone.
这是观赏日落的最佳地点。
This is the best place to watch the sunset.
你想一个人待着，为什么不去个更丑的地方?
You wanna be alone, why don't you go someplace uglier?
再说了，你不想救你的超人吗?
Besides, don't you wanna save your Superman?
我当然知道。
Of course I do.
他是我最好的朋友。
He's my best friend.
至少我是这么认为的。
At least I thought he was.
事情变化太快了，他都没告诉我他要结婚了。
Things are changing so fast, he didn't even tell me he was getting married.
你就是因为这个才心烦意乱的?
That's what's got your leash all twisted, huh?
是啊，人是很复杂的。
Yeah, well, people are complicated.
你怎么知道?
How would you know?
不,算了吧。
Nah, forget it.
你有主人。
You had an owner.
对。那是你的业务。
Right. That's your business.
我不会打听的。
I am not gonna pry.
他好吗?
Was he nice?
他们。
They.
我的主人是一家人。
My owner was a family.
♪我们都来自某个地方
♪ We all come from somewhere ♪
即使你知道♬在哪里
♪ Even when you know where ♪
一个妈妈，一个爸爸，还有她。
A mom, a dad, and her.
♪你可以依靠我♪
♪ You can count on me ♪
♬我可以依靠你
♪ And I can count on you ♪
♬这就是朋友该做的
♪ That's what friends do ♪
♪生活可以是一个很长的迷宫
♪ Life can be a long maze ♪
♪充满了美好和糟糕的日子♪
♪ Filled with good and bad days ♪
♪墙能让你有安全感♪
♪ Walls can make you feel safe ♪
♬但是他们会挡住视线
♪ But they'll block the view ♪
♪你可以依靠我♪
♪ You can count on me ♪
♬我可以依靠你
♪ And I can count on you ♪
♬这就是朋友该做的
♪ That's what friends do ♪
♬你会看到，当你的心感到空虚的时候
♪ You'll see, that when your heart feels hollow ♪
那只意味着还有房间
♪ That only means there's room ♪
♪梦想一个不一样的梦想
♪ To dream a different dream ♪
那么就让它自由吧，微笑着度过忧伤
♪ So set it free and smile through the sorrow ♪
♬你将是这个世界上最亮的光
♪ You'll be the brightest light this world has ever seen ♪
艾斯，你为那个小女孩所做的…不。那不算什么
Ace, what you did for that little girl... Nah. It was nothin'.
我只是做了所有狗都会做的事。
I just did what any dog would do.
他们就这么出卖了你?
And they just gave you away?
我不怪他们。
I don't blame them.
他们只是在保护自己的孩子。
They were just protecting their kid.
但你救了她。
But you saved her.
我还会这么做。
And I'd do it again.
这是我人生中最糟糕的一天，但我一点也不想改变。
Worst day of my life, but I wouldn't change a thing about it.
为什么不呢?
Why not?
当你爱一个人，我是说，你真的爱他，你会愿意为他做任何事。
Well, when you love somebody, and I mean, you really love them, you gotta be willing to do anything for 'em.
即使这意味着让他们离开。
Even if that means letting them go.
即使很疼?
Even if it hurts?
尤其是。
Especially then.
你知道人们是怎么说狗的吧?
You know what they say about dogs, don't you?
永远不要给我们吃巧克力。
Never feed us chocolate.
我们无条件的爱。
We love unconditionally.
对不起,先生。
Excuse me, sir.
我真的不擅长这个。
I am really bad at this.
那是因为你还在学习你的能力。
That's just because you're still learning your powers.
每个英雄都是这样奋斗的。
Every hero struggles like this.
直到他们有了训练的蒙太奇。
Until they have their training montage.
他们需要更长的蒙太奇。
They're gonna need a longer montage.
那些家伙，嗯，他们看起来很糟糕。
Those guys, well, they suck visibly.
是的,我……我同意你的观点，但他们比你想象的要强大。
Yes, I... I can agree with you there, but they're stronger than you think.
PB只需要像爱别人一样爱自己。
PB just needs to love herself as much as she loves everyone else.
Chip需要安全感。
Chip needs to feel safe.
和默顿……默顿需要绿叶蔬菜。
And Merton... Merton needs leafy greens.
你真的很了解他们，是吧?
You really know them, huh?
它叫做大学”。
It's called listenin'.
当你和一个人永远关在一起的时候，你会对他有更多的了解。
You learn a lot about someone when you're locked up with them forever.
等一下。
Wait a minute.
露露也和你一起在避难所。
Lulu was in the shelter with you, too.
你对她有什么了解?
What did you learn about her?
那个小白鼠一直在说的就是统治世界和一个手漂亮的秃子。
All that guinea pig ever talked about was world domination and some bald dude with nice hands.
莱克斯。
Lex.
当然。Stryker岛。
Of course. Stryker's Island.
她一定是去那里救他的。
She must be going there to spring him.
如果我们先到就不会。来吧!
Not if we get there first. Come on!
小心……隐形飞机。是的。
Watch out for the... Invisible jet. Yep.
也许挂个牌子。
Maybe put up a sign.
或者用绳子把它绑起来。
Or rope it off.
也许一些锥。
Maybe some cones.
入侵者。入侵者。
Intruders. Intruders.
可爱的入侵者。
Adorable intruders.
它们太可爱了。
They are so cute.
不。那是我的机器人弟弟。
No. That's my robot brother.
这是它。
This is it.
终于，我们这一代的两位天才，又在一起了。
Finally, the two great minds of our generation, back together.
你的宠物来找你了，莱克茜。
Your pet is coming for you, Lexi.
哦，不!哦,天哪!奶酪和饼干!
Oh, no! Oh, gosh! Cheese and crackers!
哦,我的天啊。神奇女侠就坐在我现在坐的地方。
Oh, my gosh. Wonder Woman has sat, like, right where I'm sitting.
事实上，我觉得我就是她，因为我站在她的位置上，坐在她的座位上。
Actually, I feel like I am her because I'm just, like, in her stance, I'm in her seat.
还有一颗花生卡在座位的缝隙里。
And there's a peanut wedged in the crack of the seat.
现在我在吃她的花生。
And now I'm eating her peanut.
更重要的是，狗能开飞机吗?
More importantly, can a dog fly a plane?
当然。我能飞，这个也能飞
Of course. I can fly. This can fly.
就像骑自行车一样。
It'll be just like riding a bike.
你会骑自行车吗?
Do you know how to ride a bike?
不，我知道怎么飞。
No, I know how to fly.
放松点，我们会没事的。
Relax, we'll be fine.
不要说!
Stop saying that!
我们永远好!
We're never fine!
是谁把我们击落的?
Who shot us down?
神奇女侠的隐形飞机是隐形的。
Wonder Woman's invisible jet is invisible.
它真的更透明了。
It's really more transparent.
胡须吗?
Whiskers?
闪开，小猫咪。我们得去斯崔克那里。
Out of the way, cat child. We have to get to Stryker's.
对不起，我不能那样做。露露救了我的命。
Sorry, I can't do that. Lulu saved my life.
现在，我必须拿走你的。
Now, I must take yours.
再见。
Goodbye.
在这里。
In here.
好的。每个人都保持沉默。
Okay. Everybody stay quiet.
哦。
Uh-oh.
——“哦”?-我要…不,没关系。
- What "oh"? - I'm gonna... No, never mind.
不，等等，没关系。
No, wait, never mind.
没关系，没关系。
Never mind, never mind.
发生了什么,帅吗?
What's happening, handsome?
拜托，我们都是成年人了。
Come on, we're both grown-ups.
别让我犹豫，好吗?
Don't leave me hanging, okay?
她会来看我们的。
Ay, she's going to see us.
PB，我需要你把身体变小一点。
PB, I'm gonna need you to get a little smaller.
我知道，我就是控制不了。
I know, I just can't control it.
就算有超能力，我也不像神奇女侠。
Even with powers, I'm nothing like Wonder Woman.
一，二，凯蒂来找你了。
One, two, kitty's coming for you.
PB，有件关于神奇女侠的事你应该知道。
PB, there's something you should know about Wonder Woman.
赞美她的名字。
Praise be her name.
戴安娜非常独立，完全是自己的女人。
Diana is fiercely independent, completely her own woman.
如果你真想像她一样，就做你自己。
And if you really wanna be like her, you'll be yourself.
我要把你撕成碎片。
I'm gonna rip you limb from limb.
好了，奇普，该点燃那只小猫了。
Okay, Chip, time to light that kitty up.
但如果恶魔激光吞噬了我呢?
But what if the demonic laser gato devours me?
还是我们所有人?
Or all of us?
还是她只会放过我，让我永远背负着生存的罪恶感?
Or she only spares me, and I forever carry the guilt of survival?
奇普，我们都会去黑暗的地方。
Chip, we all go to dark places.
我想过把露易丝·莱恩扔进海里。
I thought about throwing Lois Lane in the ocean.
但你不能把余生都困在自己的脑子里。
But you can't spend the rest of your life stuck in your own head.
你是对的。
You're right.
这里真的很可怕。
It is really scary in here.
好的。你能做到的，奇普。
Okay. You can do this, Chip.
滚出你的脑袋!
Get out of your head!
好了，我们去默顿探底吧。
All right, let's get to the bottom of Merton.
一切始于1854年的中城。
It all started in Central City, 1854.
我只是个可爱的小婴儿。
I'm just a sweet little purr-purr baby.
你为什么不和我一起玩?
Why won't you play with me?
在60年代的一段时间里，我基本上是一个全职炼金术士。
And I had a whole period in the '60s where I was basically a full-time alchemist.
默顿，我们没时间了。
Merton, we don't have time.
在这里。试试这些。
Here. Try these.
哇!
Whoa!
你们都不是乌龟!
None of you are turtles!
这解释了很多!
This explains so much!
超级宠物，出来玩。
Super-Pets, come out to play.
那个怪物该庆幸我没有热视力。
That monster is lucky I don't have my heat vision.
幸好你有更好的东西。
Good thing you've got something better.
那是什么?
What's that?
我们,你这个白痴。
Us, you idiot.
好了，收拾东西，我有个计划
Okay, pack. I have a plan.
再见。
See you in heck.
有什么事吗?
What's the matter?
你不说话了吗?
Cat got your tongue?
现在!
Now!
Boom-boom-boom。在这里,我走了。
Boom-boom-boom. Here I go.
Fast太太的裤子。
Mrs. Fast Pants.
喵,喵,buh-bye。
Meow, meow, buh-bye.
哦。
Uh-oh.
我还有八条命。
I still have eight more lives.
来吧。
Come on.
那有多有趣?
How fun was that?
一枚导弹射进了我的胸膛!
A missile was shot into my chest!
这是一种说法。
Uh, that's one way to put it.
没有别的说法了。
There's no other way to put it.
一枚导弹刚刚射进了我的胸膛。
A missile was just shot into my chest.
多亏了氪星和他的朋友，威胁被消除了。
The threat was neutered, thanks to Krypto and friends.
这是惊人的!
This is amazing!
——是的!人类保存。——不!
- Yes! Humanity is saved. - No!
我的宝宝交了朋友。
My baby made friends.
如果你们都养过宠物，就会明白了。
If you all had pets, you'd understand.
我曾经养过一只猎豹，但它吃了我的房东。
You know, I had a cheetah once, but she ate my landlord.
把我的沙发给撕了。
And tore up my couch.
我爱死那沙发了。
Man, I loved that couch.
在Oa星球上，我以为我有一只宠物浣熊，但他以为我们在约会。
On the planet Oa, I thought I had a pet raccoon, but he thought we were dating.
所有的海洋生物都是我的朋友。
All the creatures of the sea are my friends.
除了那条知道自己做了什么的鳗鱼。
Except for that one eel who knows what he did.
是啊，我不太喜欢动物。
Yeah, I'm not really an animal guy.
哦!你是过敏还是…?
Oh! Are you allergic or...?
小时候，我掉进了一个装满蝙蝠的井里。
As a child, I fell into a well filled with bats.
我还能听到它们黑色的翅膀在我周围扇动时的尖叫声，抓挠着我胖乎乎、孩子气的肉体。
I can still hear the screams as their dark wings flapped around me, scratching my chubby, childish flesh.
我醒着的每一刻都在受折磨。
I'm tormented every waking moment.
我真的认为养宠物对你有好处。
I really think a pet would be good for you.
我闻到露露的味道了。
I got Lulu's scent.
她是这样的。
She's this way.
看看你变成了一只狗。
Well, look at you being a dog.
而且，囚犯们午餐吃的是鸡蛋沙拉……穿过大厅……该死，我觉得有个机器人警卫心碎了。
Also, the prisoners had egg salad for lunch... and down that hall... Oh, dang, I think a robot guard got his heart broken.
德洛丽丝。
Dolores.
我承认，有时候这有点太具体了。
I'll admit, sometimes it can be a little too specific.
Lex !我在这里!
Lex! I'm here!
-我们终于团聚了。——停止。
- We're finally reunited. - Halt.
啊。学生回到老师身边。
Ah. The student returns to the teacher.
哦,很好。你的土拨鼠宝宝。
Oh, good. Your marmot baby.
推它。
Shove it.
我是他最喜欢的走狗，不是你，你这个…
I'm his favorite henchman, not you, you piece of...
现在，我有个礼物要送给你。
Now, I have a present for you.
不在这里，但我有它的照片。
Um, it's not here, but I have pictures of it.
失败者,失败者。
Loser, loser.
看看他们那些愚蠢的衣服。
Look at all their dumb outfits.
嗯。我消灭正义联盟的邪恶计划。
Huh. My evil plan to take out the Justice League.
哇!你真的学习了。
Wow! You really did study.
噢!等着看这个。
Ooh! And wait until you see this.
好吧，我不知道这是怎么进去的。
Okay, I don't know how that got in there.
没人想这样，对吧?
No one wants that, right?
很明显，我被黑了。
Well, clearly, I've been hacked.
好了，我带你离开这里。
Okay, let's get you out of here.
真不敢相信这一切终于发生了。
Oh, I can't believe this is finally happening.
我不敢相信这真的发生了。
I can't believe this is actually happening.
到此为止，啮齿动物。
This ends now, rodent.
你刚刚被……打败了。让我记住它。
You were just defeated by... Let me remember it.
超级宠物联盟。
The League of Super-Pets.
br, br。你好,是谁?
Brring, brring. Hello, who's there?
超级宠物联盟。
Uh, the League of Super-Pets.
露露，放弃吧。这是结束了。
Give it up, Lulu. It's over.
你白痴。你已经掌握窍门了。
You idiots. You're actually getting the hang of this.
我烤面包。我是一个落魄的人。
I'm toast. I'm a goner.
不是。
Not.
不!
No!
再走一步，小狗就成功了。
One more step and the puppy gets it.
除非你的朋友走进那边的牢房。
Unless your friends walk into those cells over there.
王牌,攻击。我会没事的。
Ace, attack. I'll be fine.
你会变成煎饼的。
You'll be a pancake.
好吧，我数到三，然后从二开始，因为我很邪恶。
Okay, I'm gonna count to three and I'll start at two 'cause I'm evil.
两个……好吧,露露。你赢了。
Two... All right, Lulu. You win.
不!别听她的。
No! Don't listen to her.
我们还有什么选择?
What choice do we have?
我不知道他们会这么伤心。
Oh, I didn't know they were gonna be so sad.
他不想进笼子，但为了救另一只，他不得不进。
He doesn't wanna go in the cage, but he has to, to save the other one.
每个人都很难过。
Everyone is upset.
♬狗狗们很伤心
♪ The dogs are sad ♪
♪乌龟难过♪
♪ The turtle's sad ♪
♬而松鼠是悲伤的
♪ And the squirrel is sad ♪
好的。我刚才说到哪儿了?
Okay. Now then, where was I?
让我看看你，我的宝贝。
Let me look at you, my pet.
哦,Lex。
Oh, Lex.
♬现在这个世界需要什么呢
♪ What the world needs now ♪
♪是爱，甜蜜的爱♪
♪ Is love, sweet love ♪
♬这是唯一的♬
♪ It's the only thing ♪
♪。♪实在是太少
♪ That there's just too little of ♪
Lex?
莱科斯，你在干什么?
Lex, what are you doing?
我们是一个团队。
We're a team.
莱克斯，我们曾经是科学家。
Lex, we were scientists together.
不。莱科斯，你在干什么?
No. Lex, what are you doing?
我是说，拜托。你不会指望我和一个啮齿动物共享荣誉吧?
I mean, come on. You didn't expect me to share credit with a rodent, did you?
Lex !
Lex!
——哦!-有点小变化!
- Oh! - Little turn of events!
♬豚鼠是悲伤的
♪ The guinea pig is sad ♪
露露，我知道你很伤心，但加入我们吧。
Lulu, I know you're hurting, but join our pack.
举起,等等!真的吗?
Hold up, wait! For real?
她把我们丢在火里等死，记得吗?
She left us to die in a fire, remember?
但如果我们齐心协力，我们就能离开这里，拯救超人。
Yeah, but if we work together, we can get outta here and save Superman.
嗯。你真的爱他。
Huh. You truly love him.
我当然知道。
Of course I do.
你是一个傻瓜。
You're a fool.
他只会让你心碎。
He'll only break your heart.
幸运的是，我要帮你一个忙，在他有机会之前毁了他。
Luckily, I'm going to do you a favor, and destroy him before he gets the chance.
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
我忘了说我邪恶计划的大结局了吗?
Oh, did I forget to mention my evil plan's grand finale?
再过28分钟，整个正义联盟就会爆炸。
In 28 minutes, the entire Justice League is gonna go kaboom.
如果我抓不到我的人，你也抓不到你的人。
If I can't have my guy, then you can't have yours.
不。我不会让你伤害他的。
No. I won't let you hurt him.
就一个问题，你被困在笼子里怎么能阻止我?
Just one question, how are you gonna stop me when you're trapped in a cage?
你也困了，天才。
You're trapped, too, genius.
是的,我知道。但就像在避难所一样，我也有逃生策略。
Yes, I know. But just like at the shelter, I always have an exit strategy.
嘿,女孩。
Hey, girl.
菜,女王。莱科斯怎么样了?
Dish, queen. How'd it go with Lex?
好吧，我现在可以这么说了，我从没喜欢过他。
Okay, I feel like I can say this now, I never liked him.
莱科斯会为他的所作所为付出代价的。
Lex will pay for what he's done.
就在正义联盟旁边。
Right alongside the Justice League.
你逃不掉的。
You won't get away with this.
我带着爱说这些。你们都是失败者。
I say this with love. You are all losers.
你们一直都是失败者，你们将继续是失败者，直到你们的失败者生命结束。
You've always been losers, and you'll continue to be losers until the end of your loser lives.
对了，克里普托，我一定会替你跟超人说再见的。
Oh, and Krypto, I'll be sure to say goodbye to Superman for you.
好,好,好。
Well, well, well.
这不是正义联盟吗，被我一个人抓住了。
If it isn't the Justice League, captured by me, entirely on my own.
豚鼠几乎什么都做了。
The guinea pig did literally everything.
是的，不得不承认，感觉不太好。
Yes, gotta admit, doesn't feel great.
但这一切都是值得的。
But it's all worth it.
因为你们这群笨蛋要完蛋了。
Because you chumps are going down for good.
没用的,
It's no use.
这些细胞被设计用来防止任何有超能力的人逃跑。
These cells were designed to keep anyone with powers from escaping.
你得像超人一样强壮才能出来。
You'd have to be as strong as Superman to get out.
我们不能就这么放弃。
Well, we can't just give up.
放弃和知道什么时候结束是有区别的。
There's a difference between giving up and knowing when it's over.
唔唔。不可能。不是超级英雄。
Mm-mmm. No way. Not for superheroes.
我不是超级英雄。
I'm not a superhero.
我甚至不是一条好狗。
I'm not even a good dog.
当我还是只小狗的时候，我答应过要照看超人。
When I was a puppy, I promised I'd watch over Superman.
我失败了。
And I failed.
都是因为我嫉妒露易丝。
All because I was jealous of Lois.
谁不会?你看到那些刘海了吗?
Who wouldn't be? Have you seen those bangs?
Ba-bang !
Ba-bang!
超人是我唯一的朋友，我害怕失去他。
Superman was my only friend and I was afraid to lose that.
但你不能责怪自己。
But you can't blame yourself.
我是唯一该受责备的人。
I'm the only one to blame.
如果我真的是他的朋友，无论发生什么事，我都会支持他。
If I really was his friend, I'd have been there for him no matter what.
我父亲是对的。
My father was right.
我的问题是我自己。
My problem is me.
我很抱歉。
I'm sorry.
不，伙计，你很好。
Nah, man, you're good.
你终于对自己坦诚了。
You're just finally being real with yourself.
没有真相就没有正义。
You can't have justice without truth.
谢谢,王牌。
Thanks, Ace.
但是已经太晚了。
But it's too late.
你确定吗，佩里托?
Are you sure about that, perrito?
你是什么意思?
What do you mean?
你的飞行。
You're flying.
什么?
What?
我…我的权力。
I'm... My powers.
我回来了!
I'm back!
氪星石已经离开了狗。
The kryptonite has left the dog.
嗯，那闻起来确实像檀香。
Well, that does smell like sandalwood.
好了，是时候拯救正义联盟了。
All right, time to save the Justice League.
让我们敲碎一些头骨。
Let's crack some skulls.
不，你已经做得够多了。
No, you've done enough.
现在说什么?
Um, say what now?
我一开始是为了救一个最好的朋友，现在我又多了四个。
I started this with one best friend to save and now I have four more.
哦!他的意思是我们。
Aw! He means us.
我不能让你们为我的错误冒生命危险。
I can't let you keep risking your lives for my mistake.
但别担心，等这一切结束，我还是会带你们去那个农场。
But don't worry, when this is over, I'm still taking you all to that farm.
小狗，快起来!
Pup, up and away!
你相信那只狗吗?
You believe that dog?
有了情感上的突破，恢复了能力，然后又恢复了。
Has an emotional breakthrough, gets his powers back, and then bounces.
-我觉得很贴心。——我也是。
- I thought it was sweet. - Me, too.
说实话，我中等，你知道的。
I'm medium on it, you know, if I'm honest.
是时候让超人死去了。
Time for the death of Superman.
我不太确定。
I'm not so sure about that.
啊!这家伙吗?
Ugh! This guy again?
最后一句话吗?
Any last words?
我喜欢这么说。
I love saying that.
最后一句话吗?哦，很有趣。
Any last words? Ooh, it is fun.
嘿。你喜欢我的小笑话吗?
Hey. You liked my little joke?
把你关在牢房里。
Lockin' you up in the cell.
很有趣，对吧?对吧?
That was funny, right? Right?
不，嘿，拜托，是我。爸爸莱克斯。
No, hey, come on, it's me. Papa Lex.
不,嘿…什么?来吧!
No, hey... What? Come on!
是啊，我的薪水可不够。
Yeah, I don't get paid enough for this, no.
锁的大门。
Lock the gates.
我可等不了那么久。
Ew, I can't wait that long.
我们现在就开始吧。我想现在就做。
Let's do it now. I want to do it now.
你确定吗?
Are you sure about this?
我是说，我们可以策划绑架案。
I mean, the kidnapping we could get behind.
我们喜欢绑架，但如果你这么做，他们会死。
We liked the kidnapping, but if you do this, they'll die.
这就是……你以为我们在干什么?
That's the point of... What did you think we were doing?
马克,基斯,受到影响。
Mark, Keith, suffer.
下台。
Stand down.
好吧，氪星，你现在绝对是在跟踪我。
Okay, Krypto, you are definitely stalking me now.
我好像被吓到了。
I'm, like, creeped out.
再见。
Bye.
飞在那里。
Fly over there.
你是说，朝着那个杀人的啮齿动物?
You mean, toward the murder rodent?
超人在哪里?
Where is Superman?
你太迟了。
You're too late.
我要把他送回他来的地方。
I'm sending him back to the place from whence he came from.
Boop !
Boop!
不!
No!
什么……这是怎么呢
What... What's going on?
是啊，有趣的故事。
Uh, yeah, funny story.
我把我的办公室变成了一艘火箭飞船。
I, uh, turned my office into a rocket ship.
所有亿万富翁都有。
All billionaires have 'em.
这是真的。
It's true.
克瑞普，火箭上有个炸弹。
Krypto, there's a bomb on the rocket.
当它离开地球大气层时，它会内爆。
When it leaves Earth's atmosphere, it'll implode.
我们只是咳嗽。走吧!
We're just coughing. Go!
我来找你了，超人。
I'm coming for you, Superman.
Uh-uh-uh !
Uh-uh-uh!
没有那么快。
Not so fast.
谁能活下来，小狗?
Who gets to live, doggy?
你爱的男人，还是他爱的女人?
The man you love, or the woman he does?
你一个人救不了他们两个。
You can't save them both on your own.
怎么了,狗吗?
What's up, dog?
这是什么?爪子巡逻吗?
Ugh, what is this? PAW Patrol?
我不是让你们待在原地吗。
I thought I told you guys to stay put.
我们什么时候听过你的?
When do we ever listen to you?
嘘!我无聊!
Boo! I'm bored!
让我们来看看猛烈的撞击。
Let's get to the fiery crash.
你节省超人。
You save Superman.
-从火箭上?-我相信你。
- From a rocket? - I trust you.
好吧，但是从火箭上?
Okay, but from a rocket, though?
大家一起跳。
Hop on, y'all.
因为这头猪就要变成火腿了。
Because this pig right here is about to go ham.
那东西带走了我们的超人。
That thing took our Superman.
她会是失望。
She's goin' down.
默顿,触及它。
Merton, hit it.
唉!
Ay!
一切都结束了,仓鼠。
It's over, hamster.
仓鼠吗?
Hamster?
仓鼠只是一元店的沙鼠。
A hamster is just a dollar store gerbil.
仓鼠是一种没有什么有趣毛皮活动的花栗鼠。
A hamster is a chipmunk with nothing interesting going on fur-wise.
你了,孩子。像开金枪鱼罐头一样打开它。
You're up, kid. Open it like a can of tuna.
我帮你松开了。
Well, I loosened it for you.
伙计，我讨厌刀枪不入。
Man, I hate bein' invulnerable.
我们开始吧。明天会疼的。
Here we go. This is gonna hurt tomorrow.
为什么我不能有弹性?
Why couldn't I have been stretchy?
或者，拿个魔法锤什么的。
Or, like, gotten a magic hammer or something.
不!
No!
面对它。
Face it.
——这是结束了。——嗯?
- It's over. - Huh?
你的超人已经不在了，现在他珍爱的小狗将要…什么?它是什么?
Your Superman is no more and now his precious little dog is about to... What? What is it?
我脸上有东西吗?
Do I have something on my face?
我长痘痘了吗?它是湿的吗?它是准备好了吗?
Do I have a pimple? Is it wet? Is it ready?
我应该把它弄破吗?
Should I pop it?
嘿,家伙。大风扇。
Hey, guys. Big fan.
嗯…你们也看到那只大猪了吧?
Um... You all see the giant pig too, right?
不。他们是怎么……?
No. How did they...?
你忘了一件事，露露。
You forgot one thing, Lulu.
不像你，我有朋友。
Unlike you, I have friends.
你说得对，你确实有朋友。
You're right, you do have friends.
但这种情况不会持续太久。
But not for long.
露露面前跪下。
Kneel before Lulu.
哦,来吧。
Oh, come on.
我说,跪!
I said, kneel!
-努力跟上，乌龟。——好的。
- Try to keep up, turtle. - Okay.
猪的生物……跟随我的领导。
Porcine creature... ... follow my lead.
蝙蝠侠独自工作。
Batman works alone.
除了罗宾，阿尔弗雷德，戈登特派员…
Except for Robin, and Alfred, Commissioner Gordon...
不要弄乱我那一半的头发!
Don't mess up my half-fro!
我是潜水侠。
I am Aquaman.
得到它,松鼠!
Get it, squirrel!
.．.正义联盟，蝙蝠女，蝙蝠女，我的IT团队，摩根·弗里曼演的那个人，啊，管他呢。
...Justice League, Batgirl, Batwoman, my IT crew, whoever Morgan Freeman played, Ah, what the heck.
看着吧，你这可怜的狗，我要毁掉你在乎的所有人。
Watch, you pathetic pooch, as I destroy everyone you care for.
无论你做什么都无法阻止我。
And there's nothing in the world you can do to stop me.
你说得对，露露，在这个世界上我没办法阻止你。
You're right, Lulu, there's nothing I can do in this world to stop you.
你在说什么，伙计?
What are you talking about, man?
你那句话的句法结构为什么这么奇怪?
And why was your syntax so oddly structured in that sentence?
帮我盯着超能力者。
Keep an eye on Supes for me.
他要去哪里?
Where's he going?
不。不是太阳能爪拳。
No. Not the Solar Paw Punch.
果汁盒的事?
The juice box thing?
但那样会害死他的。
But that'll kill him.
Krypto,不。
Krypto, no.
你说得对，艾斯。
You were right, Ace.
哇,哇!
Whoa, whoa!
我还差几个几尼就能养头猪。
I am a few guineas short of a pig.
嗯…
Uh...
啊!
Ah!
当你爱一个人，我是说，你真的爱他，你会愿意为他做任何事。
Well, when you love somebody, and I mean, you really love them, you gotta be willing to do anything for 'em.
即使很疼?
Even if it hurts?
尤其是。
Especially then.
不!
No!
伙计，当警犬护盾真没劲。
Man, it sucks being a canine shield.
现钞。
Oof.
我觉得我的牙齿还在发光。
I think my teeth are still glowing.
你救了我的命，伙计。
You saved my life, man.
你当时正忙着救我们的呢。
Hey, well, you were in the middle of saving ours.
你知道人们是怎么说狗的。
You know what they say about dogs.
看来你的超级脑壳里确实有东西。
So, something did get through that super skull of yours.
别逼我收回。
Don't make me take it back.
-滚，滚，滚。——再见。
- Bum, bum, bum. - Bye.
什么?你对我做了什么?
What? What have you done to me?
我陷入困境了，不是吗?
I'm in hot dog water, aren't I?
不!
No!
是啊!
Yeah!
谢天谢地，你没事。
Oh, thank goodness you're okay.
我为你感到高兴，伙计。
I'm happy for you, buddy.
你知道克瑞普救了我吗?
You know Krypto rescued me?
我知道这种感觉。
I know the feeling.
很久以前他救了我。
He rescued me a long time ago.
它是一只好狗。
He's a good dog.
过来,男孩。
Come here, boy.
嘿。
Hey.
对不起,Krypto。
I'm sorry, Krypto.
你知道你永远是我最好的朋友。
You know you'll always be my best friend.
没有什么能改变这一点。
And nothing can ever change that.
哦，还有一件事。
Oh, one more thing.
哇，看那个。
Wow, look at that.
这一切我都计划好了，但是…不，拜托，这就是我一直想象的样子。
I did have this whole thing planned, but... Oh, no, please, this is exactly how I always pictured it.
巨大邪恶的豚鼠。
Giant evil guinea pig.
这个…这在我的愿景板上。真的。
This... This was on my vision board. Really.
你想继续吗?
You wanna keep going?
是的,我会的。谢谢你！
Yes, I would. Thank you.
露易丝·乔安妮·莱恩，让我成为全宇宙最快乐的超人。
Lois Joanne Lane, make me the happiest Superman in the universe.
——将你……——嗯,好吧!
- Will you... - Yeah, okay!
婚前协议。
Prenup.
捏的布鲁斯!
Squeezy Bruce!
最好是有执照的玩具，不然我要疯了。
That better be a licensed toy, or I will freak out.
哦!
Oh!
嘿,别担心。我得到了你。
Hey, don't worry. I got you.
好的,发生了什么?
Okay, what's happening?
哇，这太奇怪了。
Wow, this is so weird.
如此美丽!
So beautiful!
我们都很快的时候，击掌却这么慢。嗯。
High-fiving so slow when we're both really fast. Huh.
塞米西拉的戴安娜王妃，我谦卑地向你们介绍我自己，超级猪，还在头脑风暴。
Princess Diana of Themyscira, I humbly present myself, Super Hog, still brainstorming, to you.
你会成为一个强大的战士。
You will be a mighty warrior.
和拥抱的朋友。
And cuddle buddy.
我有祸了。
Woe is me.
没人在乎那个水工。
No One cares about the water guy.
这个水工知道。
This water guy does.
嘿，我叫基斯。
Hey, my name's Keith.
小猪猪吻。
Aw, little piggy kisses.
嘿,烟。
Hey, smokey.
你看起来有点累。
You're looking a little burnt out.
需要灯吗?
Need a light?
哦，看看我!
Oh, look at me!
哦,来这里。
Aw, come here.
我是马克。和你的名字吗?
I'm Mark. And your name?
所以，你是一只狗。
So, you are a dog.
我是蝙蝠侠。
I am the Batman.
抱歉，我不太擅长和动物打交道。
Sorry, I'm not really great with animals.
是啊，我不太会和人打交道。
Yeah, I'm not really great with people.
可能是因为我的童年创伤。
Probably because of my traumatic puppy hood.
小时候，我的家人就被夺走了。
As a child, my family was taken from me.
当我还是只小狗时，我就被从我的家人身边带走了。
As a puppy, I was taken from my family.
所以，我磨练了自己。
So, I've steeled myself.
我的情绪，总是在控制中。
My emotions, always in check.
没人能通过我坚不可摧的防线。
No one ever getting past my impenetrable defenses.
啊，管他呢?
Ah, what the heck?
好男孩。
Good boy.
好吧，蝙蝠侠也爱你。
Okay, the Batman loves you, too.
哦!嘿,老爹
Oh! Hey, Pops.
是的，是我，狗-艾尔。
Yes, it is I, Dog-El.
从不吃巧克力。镜子里的狗就是你。
Never eat chocolate. That dog in the mirror is you.
烟花吸!
Fireworks suck!
替我向盖尔问好!
Tell Gail I said hey!
看来你和超人都解决了。
Looks like you worked everything out with Superman.
多亏了你的建议，我也交了一些新朋友。
Thanks to your advice, I made some new friends, too.
现在我要带他们去史摩维尔。
And now I've gotta bring them to Smallville.
我答应他们，这将是他们的新……
I promised them that it would be their new...
哦!
Aw!
……。
...home.
嘿，奇普顿-和杰西卡怎么样了?-人类和宠物的关系越来越亲密了。她甚至给它戴上了戒指。
Hey, Chip-tonite, - How's it going with Jessica? - We're getting pretty close as person and pet. She even put a ring on it.
不错的服装游戏，PB。
Nice costume game, PB.
谢谢!它甚至还有磁铁。
Thanks! It even has magnets.
这要花多长时间?
Um, how long is this gonna take?
我和两个消防员头盔有个火热约会。
I got a hot date with two firemen's helmets.
剧透一下，他们是双胞胎。
Spoiler alert, they're twins.
你迟到了。
You're late.
抱歉，我和黑暗骑士在玩捉迷藏。你见过丘伯曼吗?
Sorry, me and the Dark Knight were playing a little bit of fetch. Have you met Chewperman?
那么无礼。
So disrespectful.
你们开始。
Y'all started it.
那么，我们的任务是什么?
So, what's the mission?
我们可以回答这个问题。
We can answer that.
我们的情报显示有条狗被变异了。
Okay, our intel indicates a dog has been mutated.
这可能很危险。
This could be dangerous.
我们得阻止他。
We have to stop him.
收紧你的衣领。我们有工作要做。
Tighten your collars. We've got work to do.
我吃了那个联邦快递的家伙。
I ate the FedEx guy.
嘿，我认识那条狗。
Hey, I know that dog.
他又大又蓝，快要把我们压垮了。
He's giant and blue and about to crush us.
无法粉碎我们的感情。
Can't crush what we have.
说它回来。来吧。
Say it back. Come on.
- - - - - -来吧。-我们已经拥有的无法摧毁。
- Come on. - Can't crush what we have.
Super-Pets,激活!
Super-Pets, activate!
♬这几天我很烦躁，工作的日子没有尽头
♪ These days I'm restless Work days are endless ♪
♪看看你是怎么让我，让我
♪ Look how you've made me made me ♪
♪♪时间过得更快♪回放你的笑声
♪ But time moves faster replaying your laughter ♪
灾难♪♪
♪ Disaster ♪
♪因为现在你离我那么远，而我却倒下了
♪ Cause now you're so far away and I'm down ♪
♬感觉自己就像人群中的一张脸
♪ Feelin' like a face in the crowd ♪
♬我伸手去找你，害怕♬
♪ I'm reachin' for you terrified ♪
♪因为你可以是我爱的那个♪
♪ Cause you could be the one that I love ♪
♬我可以成为你梦想中的那个人
♪ I could be the one that you dream of ♪
♪瓶子里的留言是我唯一能做的♪
♪ Message in a bottle is all I can do ♪
♪站在这里希望它能到你身边♪
♪ Standin' here hopin' it gets to you ♪
♬你可以成为我的唯一，而我
♪ You could be the one that I keep and I-I-I ♪
♬这可能是你晚上睡不着的原因
♪ Could be the reason you can't sleep at night ♪
♪瓶子里的留言是我唯一能做的♪
♪ Message in a bottle is all I can do ♪
♪站在这里希望它能到你身边♪
♪ Standin' here hopin' it gets to you ♪
♬伦敦怎么样伦敦
♪ How is it in London London ♪
♪我在想♪你在哪里
♪ Where are you while I'm wonderin' ♪
♪如果我还能再见到你♪
♪ If I'll ever see you again ♪
♬你可以成为我爱的那个人
♪ You could be the one that I love ♪
♪现在我站在这里，希望它能到你身边♪
♪ And now I'm standin' here hopin' it gets to you ♪
♪因为你可以是我爱的那个♪
♪ Cause you could be the one that I love ♪
♬我可以成为你梦想中的那个人
♪ I could be the one that you dream of ♪
♪瓶子里的留言是我唯一能做的♪
♪ Message in a bottle is all I can do ♪
♪站在这里希望它能到你身边♪
♪ Standin' here hopin' it gets to you ♪
♬你可以成为我的唯一，而我
♪ You could be the one that I keep and I-I-I ♪
♬这可能是你晚上睡不着的原因
♪ Could be the reason you can't sleep at night ♪
♪瓶子里的留言是我唯一能做的♪
♪ Message in a bottle is all I can do ♪
♪站在这里希望它能到你身边♪
♪ Standin' here hopin' it gets to you ♪
♬你可以成为我爱的那个人
♪ You could be the one that I love ♪
♬我爱♬
♪ I love ♪
♪现在我站在这里，希望这能到达你身边♪
♪ And now I'm standin' here hopin' this gets to you ♪
喂?
Hello?
打扰一下。是我。
Excuse me. It's me.
有什么可爱的动物会放我出去吗?
Are any adorable animals going to let me out?
也许一只猫?养只猫怎么样?
Maybe a cat? How 'bout a cat?
不。
Nope.
我早就知道我的结局会是这样。
I always knew this is how it would end for me.
哦。这是你的。嗨。
Oh. It's you. Hi.
让我们诚实。
Let's be honest.
我们俩才是这次行动的幕后主脑。
The two of us are the real brains behind this operation.
忘记莱克斯。
Forget Lex.
我们应该合作。
We should team up.
你觉得怎么样?
So, what do you say?
你想住进一间小公寓吗?
You wanna come live in a studio apartment?
与你?
Like, with you?
怪癖变成情况?
Like, pet-owner situation?
让我想想。是的,是的!答案是肯定的!
Hmm, uh, let me think. Yes, yes! The answer is yes!
我只是想知道一些关于我的事。
So, just something to know about me.
我热衷于统治世界我的指甲每个月都要修两次。
I'm passionate about world domination and my nails need to be trimmed twice a month.
去捡!
Fetch!
这是我的玩具。
That's my toy.
那为什么在我嘴里?
Then, why is it in my mouth?
超人。
Superman.
黑亚当。
Black Adam.
你的主人也是个英雄?
Your owner's a hero, too?
反英雄。
Antihero.
基本上和普通英雄没什么两样，只是更酷。
It's basically exactly like a regular hero except way cooler.
你制定了自己的规则，然后又打破了它们。
You make up your own rules, and then you break them.
此外，你可以忽略大多数道德和伦理惯例，因为没有人能阻止你。
Also, you can ignore most moral and ethical conventions because no one can stop you.
是啊，听起来很像坏人。
Yeah, that sounds a lot like a villain.
反英雄。
Antihero.
如果他反对英雄，那他不就是恶棍吗?
If he's anti a hero, then isn't he a villain?
承认他是个反英雄，否则黑亚当会毁了你。
Admit he's an antihero or Black Adam will destroy you.
非常邪恶的行为。
Very villain thing to do.
这条线很好，我不撒谎。
It's a fine line, not gonna lie.
不管他是什么，我打赌他飞不了冥王星。
Well, whatever he is, I bet he can't fly to Pluto.
噢,是吗?看着他。
Oh, yeah? Watch him.
我的玩具
My toy.